

# Ahmed Derbali JUNIOR FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

in linkedin.com/in/ahmed-derbali 🥠 github.com/DerbaliA

Coming from a background in development, I love creating pages where I'm able to create enjoyable interactions and experiences for everyone! And with Coding Dojo's education and support, I can now call myself a junior Full-stack Web Developer... spending eight years working as an army officer taught me how to lead a group and many other soft skills like Punctuality, Deliberation, Practicality, and Imperturbability...

Education		
06/2024 – present	<ul> <li>Full-Stack MERN Development, Master Class</li> <li>HTML, CSS, and JavaScript (Development Fundamentals), Bootstrap, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, React.js, MERN integration, complete development (comprehensive practice) Testing and Debugging, Deployment and Maintenance (Lifecycle Management), and Practical Projects</li> </ul>	
12/2022 - 12/2023	<ul><li>Full-stack Web Development, Coding Dojo (American Certification)</li><li>Web Fundamentals / Python / JavaScript / Java</li></ul>	
2015 – 2017	<ul> <li>Master's Degree in Military Sciences, The Military Academy</li> <li>Military Subjects: Arms / Ammunition / Ballistic /Shooting /</li> <li>University Subjects: Finance / Math / Economics / Languages /</li> </ul>	
2012 - 2015	<ul> <li>Fundamental License Degree in Finance,</li> <li>Faculty of Economics and Management of Tunis</li> <li>Case Study / Corporate Recording / Strategic Business Management /</li> <li>Audit and Assurance / Tax Compliance / Financial Management / Business Planning / Financial Accounting and Reporting / Business Strategies and Technologies /</li> <li>Accounting / Management Information / Principles of Taxation / Law /</li> </ul>	

# **Technical Skills**

# Web Fundamentals (Terminal – Git /GitHub - HTML5 - CSS3 - JavaScript - jQuery (JavaScript ES6 - MongoDB - Express.js - React - Node.js - Socket.io - Tailwind CSS) Java (Java 8 - MySQL - JSP - Spring Data JPA - Spring Boot - Spring Security - (Python 3 - OOP - Flask - MySQL - Ajax) Bootstrap)

Professional Experience		
07/2023 – present	A Company Commander of the Military Academy, Tunisian Army	
07/2022 - 07/2023	An Instructor at the Military Engineering Training Center, Tunisian Army	
07/2021 - 07/2022	A Company Commander of the Engineering Corps, Tunisian Army	
08/2017 - 07/2021	A Platoon Leader of Engineering Corps, Tunisian Army	

## **Projects**

### **Computers Shop:**

• A template with only HTML and CSS. It is a company's website used for selling computers and laptops.

### Derbali\_E-Commerce\_Shop:

• An e-commerce website using MongoDB, Express js, React, node js, and Tailwind CSS as a Framework.

### **Responsive Blog App:**

• Responsive MERN Stack App with React, Node.JS, Express JS MongoDB, JWT Authentication and File Upload.

### Personal Portfolio:

• Simple Portfolio using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. You can find out a lot about CSS from this responsive portfolio, which also has a functional contact section that allows employers to email you.

# Simple Blog:

• Build a MERN CRUD APP (backend server), using MongoDB, Mongoose, and JWT authentication.

# **Responsive Portfolio:**

• A fully functioning personal portfolio website (MERN Stack) using Next.js 14 and CSS 3.

### **Simple Responsive Portfolio:**

• Responsive personal portfolio using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

